Henry DeWolf Smyth Papers 1885-1987 Mss.Ms.Coll.15
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Professional Correspondence, 1916-86
  - Hefner, Frank K.
    - Folder #2, 1965
  - Heilman, Clair, 1954
  - Heisenberg, [Werner?]
    - see Atomwirtschaft-atomtechnik
  - Heller, E., 1955
  - Helm, Carl E.
    - see Notterman, J. M.
  - Helm, Harold H., 1955-57; 1966
    - see also Princeton University. Trustees
    presidential search for Princeton
  - Hemmendinger, [?]
  - Henderson, C. L.
    - see Wilson, Robert E.
  - Henderson, Frances, 1949
  - Henderson, Herbert S.
  - Henderson, John, 1945-55
  - Henderson, John T.
  - Henderson, Malcolm
    - see Pollock, Thomas Clark
  - Hendrickson, Robert C.
  - Henehan, Joseph A.
  - Henricksen, G. C.
  - Henry, David D.
  - Henry, Laurin L., 1962-63
  - Hensell, Hester E., 1949
  - Henson, E. T.
  - Hepburn, Thelma
  - Herling, S. R., 1944
  - Herman, Albert B.
  - Herpels, S., 1970
  - Herrington, Richard, 1960
  - Hershey, Lewis B.
  - Herzog, G., 1954
  - Hesburgh, C. S. C. (Box Series I: 19)
  - Hesburgh, Theodore M., 1961; 1968
    Eklund IAEA election
  - Heslep, Charter, 1953-1962
    - Steele, Robert
  - Hess, [?], 1942
    - Cornog, R.
  - Hess, Harold F., 1952
  - Hess, H[arry] H., 1956-66
  - Hess, Lewis, 1942
    - Calingaert, George
    metal carbonyls
  - Heston, W. M., 1959
  - Hevenor, Robert H., 1965
    - see also Ser. II, Hamilton College. Honorary Degree
  - Hewlett, Richard G., 1958-76
    - O'Leary, Jean M.
    AEC historian, Smyth Report
  - Heyl, Lawrence, 1957
    - see also Princeton University. Library
  - Heyns, Roger W.
  - Hickenlooper, Bourke B.
    - see Ser. II, H-Bomb
  - Hicks, Maxine
  - Higgins, C. A., 1949
  - Higgins, Thomas J., 1955
  - High, M. E., 1945-46
  - Higinbotham, W[illy] A., 1950; n.d.
    - see also Federation of American Scientists
    - see also Ser. III, Fellowship Program
    censorship
  - Hilberry, Norman, 1942-62
  - Hill, David L.
    - see Federation of American Scientists
  - Hill, J. M., 1966
  - Hill, T. B. (Admiral), 1949
  - Hines, William, 1953
  - Hinkley, J. W.
    - see Kendall, E. C.
  - Hinshaw, [?], 1951
  - Hinshaw, Carl
    - see Williams, Walter J.
  - Hipsley, Elmer R., 1961
  - Hirsch, M. Etienne, 1959
  - Hlobil, J. S. J., 1945; 1946
  - Hoagland, Hudson
  - Hobbs, Frederick T., 1942-67
  - Hobson, Jesse E.
  - Hochgesang, Frank P., 1949
  - Hoey, Clyde R.
    - see Nordheim, L. W.
  - Hoffman, Marjorie
    - see Lavender, Robert A.
  - Hofner, [?], 1956
  - Hofstadter, Robert, 1957; 1966
  - Hogen, Shinsaku, 1966
  - Hogness, T. R., 1944
    Hanford extraction process
  - Hoitsma, Benjamin J., 1955
  - Holcomb, W. F., 1961
  - Holderman, Carl, 1955
  - Holifield, Chet, 1962-69
    - see also Ser. III, Barter Arrangements
    H-bomb decision of 1949-50
  - Holl, Jack M.
  - Hollaender, Alexander, 1949; 1950
  - Holland, Albert H., Jr., 1952
  - Holland, H. D.
  - Holliday, W. T., 1946
  - Hollingsworth, J., 1945
  - Hollingsworth, R. E., 1967
  - Hollis, Everett L., 1954
  - Holmes, Paul
  - Holt, George C., 1955; 1958; 1966
    - see also Rollins College. Conference on World Government
  - Holt, Hamilton, 1946
  - Holt, Vance R., 1954
  - Holton, William B., 1942
    UBr-4; UI-4
  - Homer, Sidney, 1965-66
  - Homrighausen, E. G.
  - Hoover, J. Edgar
  - Hope-Jones, Ronald C.
    - see Ser. IV, Financing of IAEA safeguards costs
  - Hopfield, J.
  - Hopkins, D. Luke, 1943-45
    - Schairer, Otto S.
    OSRD contracts w/Princeton & Johns Hopkins
  - Horizons Incorporated, 1950; 1955
    - Goodridge, Edwin T.
  - Horner, Richard E.
  - Hornig, Donald F., 1957; 1968
  - Horowitz, Robin, 1959
  - Horsfall, James G., 1968
  - Hotel Sheraton Park, 1958
  - Houghton Mifflin Company, 1950-54
    - Brooks, Paul
    - Leggett, John
  - Householder, Belle [M?], 1949
  - Houston, W. V.
  - Howe, John P., 1952-56
    North American Aviation, Inc.
  - Howell, Charles R., 1949-51
  - Howell, Samuel C., 1962
    - see also Pierce, J. R.
  - Howlett, Duncan, 1960
  - Hribar, Edward W., 1953
  - Huang, Chi-lu, 1965
  - Hubbard, Ruth
  - Hubel, Gordon
    - see Reingold, Nathan
  - Huberman, Benjamin, 1968
  - Hudson, Donald E., 1951
  - Hudson, Miller N., Jr., 1969
  - Hufbauer, Karl, 1969
  - Huff, William K.
  - Hughes, Phillip R., 1955
  - Hughes, R. M., 1925
    H.D.S. job offer from Miami Univ.
  - Hughes, Richard J.
  - Hughes, Rowland, 1954
  - Hull, D. E., 1942
    analysis of samples for OEMsr 412 project
  - Hull, Gordon Ferrie, 1945-46
    Smyth Report comments & corrections
  - Humelsine, Carlisle H., 1962
  - Humes, John P., 1969; 1974
  - Humphrey, Hubert H., 1958-65
  - Humphreys, Walter
    - see Massachusetts Institute of Technology
  - Hunt, Alice, 1952
  - Hunt, J. R., Jr., 1952
  - Hunt, Morton M.
    - see Ser. IX, Hunt, Morton M.
  - Huntoon, R. D., 1957-58
  - Hurd, Cuthbert C.
  - Huson, F. R.
  - Huston, Vincent G.
    - see Baxter, William J.
  - Hutcheson, J. A.
    - see Platt, Joseph B.
  - Hutchins, Robert M., 1949
  - Hutchison, A. W., 196[?]
  - Hutchison, Stanley H., 1961
  - Hutchisson, Elmer, 1958-62
  - Hutchisson, William E., Jr., 1955
  - Hyde, Donald F., 1947-65
  - Hyde, George
  - Hyde, Mary, 1973; 1976
    - Shipman, Joseph C.
  - Hynek, J. Allen, 1945
  - Iddles, Alfred (Box Series I: 20)
  - Ikerman, Ed. J., 1947; 1949
  - Inglis, David R.
  - Inouye, Goro, 1957
  - Institute for Advanced Study
    - Bigelow, Julian H.
    - McMillen, J. Howard
    - Maehly, Hans J.
    computers at Institute; lists of members
    - Folder #1, 1955-57
    - Folder #2, 1958-66
  - Institute for Defense Analyses, 1959-65
    - Christeller, Norman L.
    - Cross, Richard
    - Cusick, Paul V.
    - Leibler, R. A.
    - Norton, Garrison
    - Rosser, J. Barkley
  - Institute of World Affairs, 1953
    - Hadley, Paul E.
    - von Kleinsmid, R. B.
  - Institute on Industrial and Legal Problems of Atomic Energy, 1952-53
  - Institute on World Organization, 1954
    - Cover, John H.
  - Internal Revenue Service, 1925
  - Internat. Atom. Energy Agen. Advisory Comm. on U.S. policy on..., 1962
  - International Cooperation White House Conference
    - Jones, T. O.
    - Palfrey, John G.
    as part of Intern. Coop. Year; reports on peaceful uses of atomic energy
    - Folder #1, 1964-65
    - Folder #2, 1965
    - Folder #3, 1965
  - International Union of Pure and Applied Physics, 1957-58; n.d.
    - Atwood, Wallace W., Jr.
    - Brode, Robert B.
    - Buffalo, Harvey A.
    - Cornell, S. D.
    - Grainger, Bruce
    - Hayes, John W., Jr.
    - Murphy, Robert
    - Parrish, Catherine M.
    - Rowland, Elizabeth
    - Simonpietri, Andre C.
    - Southerland, J. Harlan
    - Wheeler, Richard S.
    includes reports
  - Internuclear Company, 1956
  - Investors Diversified Services, Inc., 1952
    - Naslund, Marjorie
  - Invitations to join, attend; assignments to write, 1957-64
    - Adams, Ruth
    - Arnold, Richard T.
    - Bergman, Lewis
    - Besanon, Robert M.
    - Blizard, Everitt P.
    - Brown, Francis
    - Carter, E. Finley
    - Clay, George R.
    - Cousins, Norman
    - Crouch, Kenneth E.
    - Dees, Sarah
    - Evett, Robert
    - Harman, Avraham
    - Henry, Laurin L.
    - Hofstadter, Robert
    - Humelsine, Carlisle H.
    - Johnson, Joseph
    - MacDonald, Alan G.
    - McGhee, Paul A.
    - McGlinsey, Laurence J.
    - Macy, John W., Jr.
    - Manor, Amos
    - Mather, Kirtley F.
    - Mudd, Stuart
    - Nachmansohn, David
    - Niebuhr, Reinhold
    - Pickett, Clarence
    - Ritey, Hector J.
    - Schiessler, Robert W.
    - Smith, James Ward
    - Thomas, Trevor
    - Turner, Edward L.
    - Tyroler, Charles, II
    - Van Houten, R. W.
  - Invitations to speak
    - Allan, Henry B.
    - Back, Gunnar
    - Baker, Louis C. W.
    - Ball, Thomas F.
    - Bettman, Iphigene M.
    - Bishop, Joseph B.
    - Bowman, J. C.
    - Brady, Thomas
    - Brookes, William J.
    - Brooks, Van Wyck
    - Bukantz, Samuel C.
    - Cabot, Henry B.
    - Christofferson, L. G.
    - Clark, Grenville
    - Cleveland, Richard F.
    - Cohn, Waldo E.
    - Colley, Allen F.
    - Compton, E. R.
    - Conover, John C.
    - Cope, Arthur C.
    - Cromwell, Jarvis
    - Davis, Nathaniel P.
    - Denker, David D.
    - Devers, Jacob L.
    - Dickson, Cecil B.
    - Dignan, Thomas S.
    - Doskocil, Albert C.
    - Drake, Francis J., Jr.
    - Dunbar, Leslie W.
    - Dunkley, Lilian B.
    - Dusheck, George
    - Earle, Edward Mead
    - Easton, Elmer C.
    - Epstein, Benjamin
    - Everett, J. L.
    - Flinn, Macdonald
    - Foote, Freeman
    - Ford, Clayton D.
    - Foulke, Roy E.
    - Friday, William C.
    - Friendly, Alfred
    - Gammell, John
    - Gardner, Florence
    - Gaus, John M.
    - Gilbert, Frederick A.
    - Goldenson, Samuel H.
    - Goldspiel, S.
    - Graham, Frank P.
    - Griffin, Donald W.
    - Gruening, Ernest
    - Hallford, Edward U., Jr.
    - Harms, Arnold
    - Hawley, Charles W.
    - Henehan, Joseph A.
    - Higgins, C. A.
    - Hoitsma, Benjamin J.
    - Holt, George C.
    - Homrighausen, E. G.
    - Horowitz, Robin
    - Howlett, Duncan
    - Huff, William K.
    - Hughes, Phillip R.
    - Hyde, George
    - Ivans, Clinton F.
    - Jacobs, Julian S.
    - Kelly, Michael
    - Kemper, John M.
    - Klees, Frederic
    - Kramm, J. E.
    - Laidler, Harry W.
    - Lemon, Harvey B.
    - Linhart, Peter
    - Loos, A. William
    - McGregor, Robert F.
    - McMahon, Brien
    - MacManus, R. B.
    - Malone, Miles S.
    - Marsh, Charles F.
    - Mathews, Robert W.
    - Mecker, A. R.
    - Melcher, Daniel
    - Mell, Mildred R.
    - Melnick, Donald A.
    - Meyer, Eugene
    - Miller, Merle D.
    - Mills, R. M.
    - Molnar, August J.
    - Morris, Alton C.
    - Morris, Edward S.
    - Munro, Dana G.
    - Nagel, Ernest
    - Nigh, George W.
    - Nuechterlein, Melvin H.
    - Osgood, Thomas H.
    - Padelford, Norman J.
    - Palmer, Robert S.
    - Peck, R. L.
    - Pierson, Ellis L.
    - Pyle, H. G.
    - Quillian, William F., Jr.
    - Rakosky, Irene C.
    - Rauh, Joseph L., Jr.
    - Reed, Jerome
    - Rogers, William P.
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor
    - Rose, E. J. B.
    - Saunders, Frederick A.
    - Sawyers, F. L.
    - Schapiro, Theodore
    - Schmutz, C. A.
    - Schuck, Victoria
    - Shain, Charles E.
    - Sioussat, Helen J.
    - Smiley, E. K.
    - Smith, Edwin S.
    - Smith, Emmitt D.
    - Smith, Gregory
    - Snyder, Dick
    - Sparks, William Douglas
    - Starr, Mark
    - Steers, J. Rich
    - Strager, Luther M.
    - Strong, Harold F.
    - Stryker, J. W.
    - Thompson, O. F.
    - Tucker, F. G.
    - Wade, Francis C.
    - Wahrenbrook, Howard E.
    - Walker, Eric A.
    - Walker, John Curry
    - Walters, Everett
    - Warner, Beatrice
    - Welsh, Richard S.
    - Widenmann, Hans A.
    - Wilkins, Ernest H.
    - Williams, Dudley
    - Wolfe, Hugh C.
    - Woods, Lawrence C.
    - Folder #1, 1945
    - Folder #2, 1945
    - Folder #3, 1945-46
    - Folder #4, 1946
    - Folder #5, 1946
    - Folder #6, 1949-51
    - Folder #7, 1953-58
    - Folder #8, 1957-65 (Box Series I: 21)
  - Iona, Mario, 1949; 1961
  - Iowa Bankers Association, 1951
    - American Banker
    - Warner, Frank
  - Ireton, H. J. C., 1959
  - Irving, Jadk H.
  - Ishikawa, Ichiro
    - see Geneva Conference. [Second]
  - Issaev, L., 1969
  - Ivans, Clinton F.
  - Ives, H. E.
    - see Wheeler, John Archibald
  - Jablonski, Henryk, 1967
    - Billig, Wilhelm
  - Jackson, J. Frank
    - see Beckerley, James G.
  - Jackson, William H.
    - see Owen, Nathan R.
  - Jacobs, Julian S.
  - Jacques, Philippe G., 1953-70
    - Johnson, Grady
    - Zook, Donovan Q.
    - see also De Palma, Samuel
    - see also International Cooperation White House Conference
    - see also Ser. IV, Apollo 12
  - Jahn, Robert G., 1975
  - Jain, H. C., 1961
  - James, John, 1950
  - Jameson, John D.
  - Jannuzi, F. Tomasson, 1962
    - see also Hara, Rei
  - Jauch, Josef M., 1954-58
  - Jauho, [Pelda?], 1959
  - Jeffries, Zay
  - Jenkins, John, 1955
  - Jenkins, Ruth E., 1942
  - Jerrems, A. S.
  - Jessup, Philip C., 1957
    - see also Ser. II, Council on Foreign Relations. Organization...
  - Jessup, Walter A.
  - Jet Propulsion Publications Program, 1955-65
    - Bailey, Herbert, Jr.
    - Charyk, Joseph V.
    - Donaldson, Coleman duP.
    - Dryden, Hugh L.
    - Kidd, Stephen
    - Marble, Frank E.
    - Nannie, W. Duncan
    - Sommerfield, Martin
    - Vivian, L. L.
    - von Karman, Theodor
  - Jet Propulsion Research Program, 1960
    - Drake, Robert M., Jr.
    - Jones, H. B.
    - Layton, J. P.
    - Nikolsky, A. A.
  - Jewell, Samuel, 1956
  - Jewett, F. B.
    - see Western Electric Company
  - Johnson, A. L., Jr., 1953
  - Johnson, Ellis A.
  - Johnson, Ernest F.
  - Johnson, Gerald W., 1965
  - Johnson, Grady
    - see Jacques, Philippe G.
  - Johnson, J. R.
  - Johnson, Jesse C., 1949-51
    - Graton, L. C.
    - Gustafson, J. K.
    - Smith, Ralph Carlisle
    - see also Shattuck Chemical Co.
    - see also Smith, Ralph Carlisle
  - Johnson, Joseph
  - Johnson, Joseph E., 1945-68
    - see also Carnegie Endowment for International Peace
    - see also Ser. II, Council on Foreign Relations. Nuclear...Strategic...
  - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1963-65; n.d.
    - see also G[or?]don, Mary
    - see also Crockett, William J.
  - Johnson, Ralph P., 1950; 1954
  - Johnson, Thomas H., 1951-57
    - Beck, Clifford K.
    - Haworth, Leland J.
    - Robbins, Marcus
    - Stevenson, John D.
    - Waterman, Alan T.
    - see also Allison, Samuel K.
    - see also Kaplan, Joseph
    - see also Waterman, Alan T.
    - see also Zinn, W. H.
    photochemical methods of isotope separation; accelerators; cosmotrons
  - Johnson, Walter J., 1983
  - Johnson, Warren C., 1950-58
    - Burke, J. E.
    papers on uranium
  - Johnson, Wesley M.
    - see Turner, Louis A.
  - Johnson and Johnson, 1955-56
    - Billings, O. B.
    - Brickman, L.
    - Fead, William A.
    - Kuhl, Otto A.
    - Lycan, W. H.
    - Morris, V. N.
    H.D.S. consultant to
  - Johnston, L. E. (Bill), 1954
  - Johnston, W. D., Jr., 1969
  - Johnstone, R. L.
    - see Ser. II, Forrestal Administrative Committee
  - Johnson, Lyall
    - see McDaniel, Paul W.
  - Joint Committee on Atomic Energy
    - Brobeck, William M.
    - Conway, John T.
    - Gunn, John O.
    - Holifield, Chet
    - Kehoe, Matthew W.
    - McKinney, Robert M.
    - Murray, Thomas E.
    - Shugg, Carleton
    - Toll, David R.
    research in nuclear energy; reports, remarks, & testimonies before JCAE
    - Folder #1, 1949-56
      fissionable materials; weapons production; Soviet progress in thermonuclear energy
    - Folder #2, 1957
      foreign policy & U.S. nuclear power program; atomic energy legislation
    - Folder #3, 1958
      gas cooled graphite moderated reactors
    - Folder #4, 1958
      civilian power reactor development program; radiation hazards
    - Folder #5, 1958 (Box Series I: 22)
      civilian power reactor program
    - Folder #6, 1958
    - Folder #7, 1959
    - Folder #8, 1959
      Stanford Linear Accelerator; Aircraft Nuclear Propulsion Program; bio. & envir. effects of nuclear
    - Folder #9, 1960
      Plowshare Program; Project Oilsand; nuclear explosives in mining; industrial chemicals
    - Folder #10, 1961-67
  - Joliot, G.
  - Jones, [?]
    - see Cleveland, Harlan
    - see O'Donnell, Ashton J.
  - Jones, Alexander E., 1965
  - Jones, Frances F., 1965
  - Jones, H. B.
    - see Jet Propulsion Research Program
  - Jones, Kathleen, 1964
  - Jones, Lily Murray
    - see Phi Beta Kappa Associates
  - Jones, Peter, 1956
  - Jones, R. J.
  - Jones, R. L.
  - Jones, Ronald K.
  - Jones, T. O., 1950; 1957
  - Joseph Henry Center
    - Bailey, Herbert S., Jr.
    - Birchenall, E. C.
    - Brown, T. Wistar
    - Carver, T. R.
    - Embrey, Lee Anna
    - Gillespie, Charles C.
    - Holland, H. D.
    - Kennedy, John L.
    - Moe, Henry Allen
    - Power, Eugene B.
    - Reingold, Nathan
    - Ripley, S. Dillon
    - Suratt, Samuel T.
    - Warfield, G.
    - Wilder, Mary
    - Wilks, S. S.
    - Folder #1, 1959-60
    - Folder #2, 1965-68
      APS; papers of J.H.
  - Jossem, E. Leonard
  - Joyce, J. Wallace, 1968
  - Jury, J. T.
    - see Corrosion Chemical Company
  - Kahler, Frederick A., 1951; 1960 (Box Series I: 23)
  - Kaiser, H. R.
  - Kalman, Eugene, 1950
  - Kamino, Kinnosuke, 1957
  - Kane, John H.
  - Kapitza, Peter L., 1966
    - see also Handler, Philip
    newspaper article re:
  - Kaplan, Joseph, 1954-57
    - Odishaw, Hugh
  - Kaplan, Norman, 1963
  - Karapetoff, Vladimir, 1945
  - Karl, C. L., 1944
    HDS at Univ. of Chic. Met. Lab.
  - Karl, Clarence L., 1947
  - Kassler, Betty
  - Kassler, Kenneth, 1956
  - Kastenmeier, Robert W., 1959-60
  - Katz, Donald L., 1954
    - Martin, Joseph J.
  - Katz, Sherman, 1967
    misc. HDS comments
  - Katzenbach, [?], n.d.
  - Kauffman, Jack
  - Kaus, Peter E., 1945
  - Kawashima, Yoshio, 1968
  - Kaysen, Carl, 1967
  - Keating, Cornelius F.
  - Keefe, Denis
  - Keefe, W. T., Jr.
  - Keeney, Barnaby C.
  - Keepin, G. R., 1965-67
  - Kehoe, Matthew W., 1965
  - Keim, Chris P., 1949
  - Kelehan, J. L.
  - Kelehan, James L.
  - Kelhoffer, Arthur L., 1946
  - Keller, Charles A., 1946
    OSRD contracts W/Princeton
  - Keller, Geoffrey, 1963
    - Dukes, T. A.
  - Kelley, James B., 1962
  - Kelley, Stanley, 1965
  - Kelley, W. E., 1949; 1950
    - Fackenthal, Frank D.
    - see also Warren, Shields
    Brookhaven
  - Kellogg, J. M. B., n.d.
  - Kellogg, Paul
    - see Survey Graphic
  - Kelly, Harry C., 1960
  - Kelly, Mervin J., 1957; 1958
  - Kelly, Michael
  - Kelly, William C., 1968
  - Kemper, John M.
  - Kendall, E. C., 1956-65
    - Hinkley, J. W.
    - Schauer, Charles H.
    - Sittig, Marshall
    - Wallace, John H., Jr.
  - Kenna, [?], 1957
  - Kennan, George
  - Kennedy, John F., 1961; 1963; n.d.
  - Kennedy, John L.
  - Kennedy, Joseph W., 1954
  - Kennedy, Richard T., 1983
  - Kennedy, William F., 1956
  - Kent, Norton A., 1923
  - Kerney, James, Jr., 1945
  - Kerr, Paul F., 1942
    beryllium production
  - Kerst, D. W.
  - Kester, Robert V., 1957
  - Keyes, Geoffrey, 1953
    Weapons Systems Evaluation Group
  - Keys, David A., 1951
  - Kidd, Charles V., 1957; 1959
  - Kidd, Stephen, 1964
    - Patton, J. R.
  - Kikuchi, [?], 1957
  - Kikuchi, Masashi
    - see Fund for Peaceful Atomic Development, Inc.
  - Kiley, J. P., 1952
    - Shaw, David F.
    Hanford Plant
  - Kilgore, H. M., 1945
  - Killian, James R., Jr., 1957
    - see also Massachusetts Institute of Technology. Dept. of Physics
    - see also Ser. II, Atoms for Peace Award - H.D. Smyth
  - Kilpatrick, John R.
  - Kimpton, L. A., 1944; 1957
  - Kincaid, John
    - see Sole, D. B.
  - Kinder, Ralph P., 1946; 1961
  - Kinderman, E. M.
  - King, Howard N.
  - King, Percival L. D.
  - King, W. James
  - Kingdon, K. H., 1945-55
  - Kingsley, Clifford P.
    - see Bank of New York
  - Kinney, C. R., 1947
  - Kinney, H[erb] L., 1968
  - Kinsey, E. L., 1957
  - Kintner, E. E.
  - Kintner, William R.
  - Kinzel, Augustus B.
  - Kipp, Donald B., 1964; 1966
  - Kirk, Thomas
  - Kirkman, Robert W., 1946-47
    - see also Boswell, Elizabeth M.
    Espionage Act, 1940; list of classified docs.
  - Kirkpatrick, E. C.
    - see Peterson, Carl W.
  - Kirkpatrick, Sidney D., 1953
  - Kissinger, Henry A., 1955-57
    HAK ms. "Diplomacy & limitation of Armaments"
  - Kistiakowsky, George B.
    - see McCormack, James, Jr.
  - Klauder, John R., 1970
  - Klauder, Louis T., 1949
    - Gibbs, Clarence D.
    - Henderson, Herbert S.
    - Hendrickson, Robert C.
    - Herman, Albert B.
    - Milnamow, Arthur
  - Klees, Frederic, 1954; 1955
  - Klein, A. C., 1945
    Smyth Report criticism
  - Klopsteg, Paul E., 1950; 1957
  - Kluger, Richard, 1967-68
    N.P. Davis ms. "Lawrence & Oppenheimer"
  - Kluych, Alex R., 1949
  - Knebel, Fletcher
    - see Look
  - Kneeland, H. K., 1945
  - Kneller, George F., 1956
  - Knerr, Henry W., 1951
  - Knight, O. A.
    - see Congress of Industrial Organizations
  - Knorr, Klaus E., 1957
  - Knowlton, David C., 1949
  - Koch, H. William, 1968
  - Koch, Hans Henrik, 1967
  - Koether, Mary, 1956
  - Kohnstamm, Max, 1958
    - see also Butterworth, [?]
    EURATOM
  - Kolstad, George A., 1951-64
    misc. nuclear research; Princeton Van de Graff accelerator
  - Kone, Eugene H., 1964
  - Korff, Serge A., 1962-67
  - Kowarsky, [?]
  - Kramers, Hans A., 1950-51
    Norwegian-Netherland cooperation in nuclear physics
  - Kramm, J. E.
    - see Invitatins to speak
  - Kratz, H. R., 1942
  - Kratzer, Myron B., 1963-70
    - Sheldon, Everett B.
    - see also Emelyanov, Vasilii Semenovich
    - see also Friedland, Sidney
    AEC; Tarapur Project; bilateral safeguards
  - Kraus Periodicals, Inc.
  - Kraus, Charles A., 1942
    UCl-4
  - Kretzmann, Edwin M. J., 1966
  - Krieger, Joseph
  - Kruger, P. Gerald
    - see Barschall, Heinz H.
  - Kruglak, Haym, 1950
  - Kruskal, Martin, 1958
  - Kubo, Ryogo, 1957
  - Kuebler, Clark G., 1947
  - Kuhl, Otto A.
  - Kuhn, David, 1951
  - Kunitz, Han A., 1945
  - Kuper, J. B. Horner, 1968
  - Kuper, Mariette
  - Kursunoglu, Behram, 1967
  - Kurtz, Howard G., Jr., 1957; 1959
  - Kusaka, Shuichi, 1949
    - Stratton, Henry M.
  - Labowitz, Allan M., 1970 (Box Series I: 24)
  - Lacey, John S., 1944; 1945
    ODRS patents & inventions
  - Ladenburg, Rudolf, 1941
    uranium research
  - LADSIRLAC, 1957
    - Chandler, G.
  - Lagerfelt, K. G., 1966
  - Laidler, Harry W.
  - Lakin, Frank C.
    - see Ser. III, Russian atomic explosions
  - Lamb, Arthur B., 1945
  - Lamb, Richard G.
  - Lampert, J. B., 1946
  - Lanahan, Tom
  - Landau, L.
  - Landin, Charles R.
  - Landis, John W., 1956; 1961
  - Landman, David, 1964
    Forrestal brochure
  - Landon, S. Whitney, 1957
  - Landsberger, E. K. Georg, 1961
  - Lane, Alfred C., 1947
  - Lane, Earl F., 1957
  - Lane, George H., 1966-67
  - Lane, James A.
  - Lane, W. H., 1947
  - Langguth, Paul O., 1957
  - Langmuir, David B., 1947-54
    high energy bombardment of heavy elements; quantity production of neutrons
  - Langmuir, Irving, 1942
  - Lannutti, Joseph E.
  - Lansdown, Brenda
    - see Brookings Institution
  - LaPlant, Bryan F., 1951; 1954; 1955
  - Laporte, Otto
  - Lapp, C. J., 1961
  - Lapp, R. E., 1947; 1948
  - Larsen, Carl W.
  - Larsen, Jack, 1955; 1964
  - Larson, C. E., 1952; 1971
  - Larzelere, Henry, 1949
    - Gableman, George M.
  - Lasky, Victor, 1955
  - Lassen, N. O., 1952
  - Lauderbeck, [?], 1955
  - Laughlin, Ledlie I.
  - Lauritsen, Charles C., 1964
  - Lauritsen, T.
  - Lautenberg, Frank R., 1986
  - Lavender, Robert A.
    - Hoffman, Marjorie
    - Nichols, M. H.
    - Pimentel, George C.
    - see also Feynman, Richard P.
    - see also Ser. V, Envelope 1 - Lavender, Robert A.
    OSRD patents
    - Folder #1, 1943-45
    - Folder #2, 1945-47
  - Laves, Walter H. C.
    - see Ser. II, Council on Foreign Relations. U.S. Foreign...
  - Law and Contemporary Problems, 1954
  - Lawrence, Ernest O.
    - Folder #1, 1941-42
      choosing central lab. for S-1; ion research; Westinghouse; separation & tuballoy projects
    - Folder #2, 1942-50; n.d.
      OSRD proj. SSRC-5 reports; tuballoy; S-1 personnel; graphite grids; accelerators producing free
  - Lawrence, William V.
  - Lawson, C. A., 1952
  - Lay, James
  - Layton, J. P.
  - Lazellieve, [?], 1955
  - Leachman, Robert
  - Lead, Robert J., 1955
  - Leahy, Robert E.
    - see Pryce, M. H. L.
  - Leake, Chauncey D., 1945-63
    - see also Ser. III, [Fermi Award to Oppenheimer]
  - Lederer, Ludwig G., 1952-59
    - Bowen, I. S.
  - Lederman, Leon M., 1962
  - Lederman, Leonard L., 1960-61
  - Lee, Rensselaer W., 1962
  - Lee, Shih-Mou, 1965
  - Lee, William S., 1967
  - Leeb, Brian P., 1966; 1968
  - Leenhouts, Hugh D., 1964
    - see also White, Milton G.